[{"topicId":"19","id":"19000","langCode":"en","question":"RZi0BUNs1CQHdUO+feFdQ/+H7XoD7PyawYt84ZBwAC4fbbvEGGmiR/PY/rPXnohWVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["get","would get","wouldn’t get","won’t get"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19uhgwNiFq7VotTGrHrjeWGvzU6NOeC1/1IJFUu+c+JXmrJk33IpmKXIH26JTGsTDzL5xO6HN03KQk0S2SHTX4Hll4F/rGzvg64fv+9F1tbPZhTIkA1Orsi/SrZoWaIoqLXCsFbk2N9np0DHXoyPI++BWMv7JR4zU3O+fg8F86WBsL4b+6l+2MHnK3gH5oIl2/mE77Y3cCvHG6Kc9AXuNiHjgb89N4cYDJzT/QvHusgcgNcQkYpV//Qbq5C0eozjHDzC/IIXbbTg6UZHR4D2PHLZhqubLiZZ1gw/KmqQZk1ubVrGg5xTCL/bDcLnmE7Uk6oxhw5nK8640v/oaktlEza2kBbMKnAQUIs1iH9Xq+Dbg7RvTdmOMijzOhmG7EyH5NY8fa/HZMehwFZZYIN/adZUiefxOHBCk1F36VuXWES0"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19001","langCode":"en","question":"B8PhyHRLwW9a00E43jJfxyXUZHagar3uzx4NwKFCXOLSaz1JwhqOCG1x8PT3S+9eUuZsi7ArckZJbn77P+GJ0A\u003d\u003d","answers":["go","would go","wouldn’t go","will go"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15buLVbQuXEeOLahjkp64ju7hV3nWnyBZTZlKEywJTsfDDDGXetYqWgMTbnkojdh5qmDrqx7a0xZUcC24GOrsv89xFmW9NhmFffPW2Dvt1lyxVG5/wke78+Jzu7YU0dOUi2B+XzhLMmXQp4dNoIvxi+4Tsy/SRp0NiiD6Y8Vfa14SioqekikgpkzIGWrAjXxdKwLBHC7MCVXPzMRCI4fTNeIzJBLCkjppAwlbcGa4jPTavG+6H/7V8580oKTn7/qgdsUKQGq6fmCDSSXO6e9SCOqO7N6t4p73lGOj93MJCLMN/TelbskuHXm+wGWEgIF0n7jKg7vFmfaDqBxibYBlKP6Oi9E8kWL+f1uXUvRQygH4lnOXl3Vvu/LxoQofDWSjULbplLvoVu+QAZYIWh494sathLrZiWnbe5G+5CGrgzW"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19002","langCode":"en","question":"6PCXFF7c5aIcocQgzvO+lE2keQ3iuWmnZmV5iczLYbJTscemgquoZymFM3C6Cfv5ptOuYKJGucTxyiiH1AOv85aJV06uAMVLd+/jPiw5kTo\u003d","answers":["had to","would have to","will have to","would have had to"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14kyNBXpQsI93ENrwIZi2ClolxNkJpCHG1Kw7PnKULfeK2Gjlcx4rCEg0FiVp+FAgnlN/rvgTdiFt0alS0tI/j7vpIRGu7QjfByNtLnwYUxup/TNv5uXUEq7i8dc0FAt8juvNCbHQntFX7VJ6c95PmmgatddlewhGUeZ7kEhRasyXnS86LhljGVnRH1p5mx5rN0coa3kCeR175GxKgjBnx9chRwqshmuF5Am/qlEVywjXA+Q//jWjPh/liSojKQrgu2nJCOShj9EEGR5IYLFmwd8dP1rUOmBcHzJVBTa5zfdpmXKtH1/beOWMuPU4c1X/NV8RMkqwwgETcCciKs0bgamrclCpPRi9VfusNN97jeGaO4m7+Meej3WIzUJ3ut+VhDOVHUaxCfqjFMIQNfP4MOzovxz/9nWBcTvSOOws360"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19003","langCode":"en","question":"WXCfbdSUj2CA9nQwaL2sz8Nh0MXVNJeArww/ILO+hEzs9WR/zr8JmUw++x4kJI4RVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["wouldn’t have  worn","should wear","would have worn","shouldn’t wear"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zaWElA3vxzcbryUSkU2DvfE2HTAiITYU4q0C6E7E/XAmrJk33IpmKXIH26JTGsTDzL5xO6HN03KQk0S2SHTX4Hll4F/rGzvg64fv+9F1tbPZhTIkA1Orsi/SrZoWaIoqLXCsFbk2N9np0DHXoyPI++BWMv7JR4zU3O+fg8F86WBsL4b+6l+2MHnK3gH5oIl2/mE77Y3cCvHG6Kc9AXuNiHjgb89N4cYDJzT/QvHusgcgNcQkYpV//Qbq5C0eozjHDzC/IIXbbTg6UZHR4D2PHLZhqubLiZZ1gw/KmqQZk1ubVrGg5xTCL/bDcLnmE7Ukz8sZX4RiRpwJII6dZGYovmsQjM+4bqNyz9n+JdLnUq9cG4OByKFsjuwWkaFws8V+12Gjf/7ZunwH5PdMvXbnGvGxxslHp387KzG+ZHj2e48NtbFH/8zW0zzxMJIOr+G7MpfJAoyV//0xJ+Mm0KkPipLXD8EM7f3sH1my/VXB0zIhiuObEKU7pAtf+rwJbzBHPbasocUoSfc0nKwfSnwI3qfVqyMK7sYgKS5ML9XPevapq3JQqT0YvVX7rDTfe43hmjuJu/jHno91iM1Cd7rflYQzlR1GsQn6oxTCEDXz+DDs6L8c//Z1gXE70jjsLN+tA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19004","langCode":"en","question":"yRZEedGaREPh3SpBdrZ9NJBV1RlW7JRQLDfiENR48WsBqrdOoFlw3o72dqkTwbRB","answers":["would have lost","wouldn’t lose","may lose","may not lose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1y9C0AtS75URCCzn46D9yT1BDJTK9sLRy8OnCsBUs2YqmeJ/TBjw0rFzkjpFRSM0oTTnSFqoN4Bp/0Ci70AK3XEcelTQe7+wzmroXNUFKnIo7oNQtR+ITbInw0UVMWQcTxxVwLPM5R4jNWoEzmPIIHJr4AAjaVJV0xMvlqHG2gOAi9piNiASFIkNVTdENyJrUL3JCAqMXphlbNSUitfalzlSZ7ChKVBt2yCJk0/LdnFXqHkXRhbByqtestpr44BvBlrLhaMDS0dVRVXuf0/CPmNUmIW3z1jZ3CeFqIlNeEqx8toEuOeNbGpclPVb0PAzan3tIZ25siVrAfkjSpyoLvUSnurMkB1Za98bGy8U1NOOzzRsg+x9PbYxljx9432iIzoFBqb5WqC1Nn/cvWPqBxaXrNzJaTEATF6Tf6KqzaUSp+MYVHw9bi6F0SPRZKCQ93x5VM5yrIuBhlCeK6/eFa67oDtvdVgRAsBAXcPH1seIaYjXXpWaH7zzm040uO95j+DI0ZyVErL3D+Gj1TSjKjOSSEu0uaFq7Ik6q9a298i44Z7g4yl1tIt/hGQWcMFWNyoUan6N5k2nNtXSsUtOmF710xMLtcbKsUmggQl82EAzxRsH7hOX8DhUs3Hq8edgHQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19005","langCode":"en","question":"PZsAP09t6w2P6lR+f9QXaovVhAZq8MudXzQTEWweRwt0s6B0O+6RnAKPBo4ovLrMvCZpl9EWDxjqVeMa3akBwg\u003d\u003d","answers":["would come","won’t come","would have come","will come"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/Rv900h7J8c041bR82ukJuXkI2dICGHmDz2wKhuRv7BIy5qayCHQ+KekU91TMQIRWu27raocGSQTiT13PWoubA1End97Wmj5oSH1dSXbwiBB72OQfNdQtA+AnETN1r/S2qLFMA/eECL4Rki4JFmPSCoZnxbwMAJ4HgJsXuauEdHPvo9X1KUADDBZJPcQCA5LEGgYkn3b9ghibMx14Azr1mCDF/a7IbruoCI9c1EeYpdolp46XIV8Fb9XGftAJQkudiFqaL0hPql6EdeWhSRwun82aFnqiGYnZs0WhJanaM++EckUJ9zF5KpSb/DkkW8mOK+G4SVwu2m7FqSLkjvdvrM/QdyRd39HQiABXds+J5KgUaOtp5S3wGyyQ6YnFaJOA91Z4mynB7dPUukPzMIW4+pqTlKtAWQaMILeN0ciGlW"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19006","langCode":"en","question":"1Q599dD2vcH2KJwtubKejNuk+UryoaEivhI1RuSzx7RFt/Wm0xHstSQuAKIvM7vT+YVAnUkqTm2IKrdFupQeag\u003d\u003d","answers":["would have been","will be","be","would be"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xU0o/A1Skayd2CDb9n+aV9YCe+A160v5lGVKAIt8kzSDDDGXetYqWgMTbnkojdh5qmDrqx7a0xZUcC24GOrsv89xFmW9NhmFffPW2Dvt1lyxVG5/wke78+Jzu7YU0dOUi2B+XzhLMmXQp4dNoIvxi+4Tsy/SRp0NiiD6Y8Vfa14SioqekikgpkzIGWrAjXxdKwLBHC7MCVXPzMRCI4fTNeIzJBLCkjppAwlbcGa4jPTavG+6H/7V8580oKTn7/qgdsUKQGq6fmCDSSXO6e9SCOqO7N6t4p73lGOj93MJCLMN/TelbskuHXm+wGWEgIF0j9OCncd4k+LALzij8Knhjc6PKoLdaUU848OcEXPDqtTBb8aARxoXP1lVdKvtRPaSUgckWObHPibazzARbN4Vp2kZpRbN599WYnG0swssLD6"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19007","langCode":"en","question":"EhC7ClhnGCoBuyU+gqW+eFRYctyyJ4Vj1jfdPL1NDtbjsuVtg1cSAKSbr1OdEfrJ","answers":["wouldn’t come","comes","would have come","would come"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xC0XKoQvN+K8sK6QWO42kxClHNABM8G0Bp3iDav8qbzl3jUTFkLdZ7io7IcR7r5IUXvSRTUYfiXY7sTIRkD1VM6FHa4zu4u1G/svd3pqdmEbKjNfHjRevyiK8LeWtFK2omuJvun3bfWfq3BdHRwcW32yIQWEJEIqdkM6Lle9ygTxQXipOa1YAlOzqKWGIKCSaBbaQttWNX+gq48g2FmcNW1KA1n5i7yCoyseyC33INWIhB8j/HTZTleGyW/HS7k/ZOV82o93kizRskRFVqPDAhmY/4/Vl4c2/mtSzQryuz945mTYefvxwmQPn6fiGpIlKjU1NtNDPwpqVaDy3tbXyg\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19008","langCode":"en","question":"UENH0ePp3cf8yX7pXXJ/9vczf7BGubAe+WkOLS7GpGFuM1Rl/GwQGgrSstPKJxDz","answers":["would have spent","wouldn’t spend","would spend","spends"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15O6R28vwpB25pBW5/mqHcTQVVOCEwb8K4kZG3T89sNaMoB933nuqLWEV0t0VmPHQEc8ozzh7aN9CyCT3iBh15o9PxQzHcv9yRg0okkk6cC38MT4fyHLjUAEH724boK2CANEixBfh00IlVurzM42+aIEzyYSB6qPqrArIhKB5BiU3iHKtg6ZGjE4nDmeZLPgtOV/0KJJ/9eTnQEIkY4cSlglXASDE+j7Gj6UQ7fxahOe66h03K2I964g17sQvQJyaCnswDKRwuoI5JjAzyKOSkQ6PKoLdaUU848OcEXPDqtTTEeYwy83BFZCRhfS/3FsYAjfLHHyto1uToLdmZSxuEE\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19009","langCode":"en","question":"5aFvhsyVZNstHLDZXj3KD7TK3oAppEPbu4XT3YvWSMstJ+ckzAzLpuReQbgSr0KGT7vnHOcmEb2eBjt2+kV4dCKCmqG5sCs+z6xbO8RtnbE\u003d","answers":["bought","will buy","buy","would buy"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2z/7ai34gl5DJn4fRiCQfqncC4o9baxGc0X5tf3kNFPxAoJBKDCi7PrqY2dOPSXIMCI6aLaO9NKsuI7106t0eXWapi/wyVPxcHi9+mUq0qL0N9Kld6KcewRK75DXMIWpNzFrxXOUMY/sNJh0drja48F3TNV96Ow8RUO40BRwU/oKixI1BIxeotLWTu+FRvSxKDd0s6hFad+1HnrSkLKPEFvlazsp7L6cGLcHXccygd5J3qu3dNxM9i2p5cCKRiRGOE7Jr0d+MwgqjLwPO62LcHfllP5glKFik5joisID36gDvaSIVd0REEj8gemd6E3YtxC886JDGW+HnWsvga1jY0Pm8J+nkQBQZQOhEnc6tizK0RUsowZAp6zCUlRnEwlC47rhMO/rKwvC9q7QQ+PSlzABuZ9LMu7tVbttLZQrCS6+Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19010","langCode":"en","question":"65ZEhwoKebc04mY4Y+Gw04NVHowKhuZOEywDJIVZkmzZbn1HZtRQFpdfsa1bzQ9jdw2JkE4j/5PHhyUu6XJMiw\u003d\u003d","answers":["leave","will leave","would leave","would have left"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2z/7ai34gl5DJn4fRiCQfqncC4o9baxGc0X5tf3kNFPxAoJBKDCi7PrqY2dOPSXIMCI6aLaO9NKsuI7106t0eXWapi/wyVPxcHi9+mUq0qL0N9Kld6KcewRK75DXMIWpNzFrxXOUMY/sNJh0drja48F3TNV96Ow8RUO40BRwU/oKixI1BIxeotLWTu+FRvSxKDd0s6hFad+1HnrSkLKPEFvlazsp7L6cGLcHXccygd5J3qu3dNxM9i2p5cCKRiRGOE7Jr0d+MwgqjLwPO62LcHfllP5glKFik5joisID36gDvaSIVd0REEj8gemd6E3YtxC886JDGW+HnWsvga1jY0Pm8J+nkQBQZQOhEnc6tizK0RUsowZAp6zCUlRnEwlC47rhMO/rKwvC9q7QQ+PSlzABuZ9LMu7tVbttLZQrCS6+Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19011","langCode":"en","question":"/MEvv44k/9tnBv+Cjkpky2e2jCqAyeC4SVe7Ft3uC/9ph4AqxFFoVT0Htj5XRqegEma9S0olWum0/Nf0z6CdY6pvpcGXMhqUX5MVgZZhru9kwiihhZ0XGs4yh7Hz8URh","answers":["ask","would ask","asked","will ask"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2wMYT2KATBKBPzsf3dmf7qbcC4o9baxGc0X5tf3kNFPxAoJBKDCi7PrqY2dOPSXIMCI6aLaO9NKsuI7106t0eXWapi/wyVPxcHi9+mUq0qL0N9Kld6KcewRK75DXMIWpNzFrxXOUMY/sNJh0drja48F3TNV96Ow8RUO40BRwU/oKixI1BIxeotLWTu+FRvSxKDd0s6hFad+1HnrSkLKPEFvlazsp7L6cGLcHXccygd5J3qu3dNxM9i2p5cCKRiRGOE7Jr0d+MwgqjLwPO62LcHfllP5glKFik5joisID36gDvaSIVd0REEj8gemd6E3YtxC886JDGW+HnWsvga1jY0Pm8J+nkQBQZQOhEnc6tizK0RUsowZAp6zCUlRnEwlC47rhMO/rKwvC9q7QQ+PSlzABuZ9LMu7tVbttLZQrCS6+Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19012","langCode":"en","question":"JP1BpJU8Z41IZok21vPLm7hMAp2htJud5NoCJunKzV5wQXetI8ZebKW7+jtBj761","answers":["could take","will take","takes","would have taken"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11IiIba9bynkMItVdPidQggxHHeBI8SkSpnzX+VkwTSnYENwcNb1zfz1h3EGkNo7Dt5VfZ7xmiggUg6b+DSiR59wLij1trEZzRfm1/eQ0U/ETHFZAv4za0mLSCiiH7ftseDBqOYdXvO+HXI6qvAhaDc76cYInpdXKu11cYSavOGhC90DTgNXY/WfKnYY7T0/Y118IlDmGyjKsnF2GrK9qFp1ZwbYh9eamSYeEVJRqoBEmdoygpOG4uXOsSAgNNMX7B/t5vIMhRcMLZGiKVTmIvk//agENvoR0z+LTmUvWb6zu8Z79BuwQTGGMuex0DshdGJ8KKEnkd+GBRMn24PkPoS4bXFAaolvEB073EwjWgb6xvs2ofuYrncvdCp51NdhwvPWjStJhncxaGIS/whuhVV5MwGIAlPrukHVMllekXR6+vxdt6jfgVoSXgll8InJjg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19013","langCode":"en","question":"QQZOFCtgebYHc0IXTMWoJgU2Ek6/IRGEUNj2Lh7BPJ7m4dvKxkXkGls1ibbsFBuWcbHcz3CnemplfPiP4rLDZQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["might do","does","will do","would have done"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17O+alozBySXjVwwr6jh/SUHjku7gi1ONsXypEnMY0hfiOmi2jvTSrLiO9dOrdHl1rndb1AMgX8X20uvhcWJXKID9sRxGh+DooArvkHOgnfaf7Vbs9gwww2KtcOsN7gM0F3jekA73CbHKJ2NLGEt68k3phKN/2opVZ4g0JAHg2PQU+nX0lKFV14gmAjL/8oj+gAv2wV4/L7ySN1fDQq6rj4GXv8dWtaTTKRoT7TeXU+BYyfb1eiRUTB65l9JlPeRRpfYbf0X3JRJm3KMYGutDmZwwn/YKXxzkP7BXmHcrXDCp2TbV+mR/6zcstKtEPHcqPvYr/B7TkqxMCsdsZ9FtFsWSGhRoiKg0jBw6i7b+pDfebSUYf5Yomt+qZpfyQQGU/QU1VpjFvFN+WD3zvNt/rN/Tbm9+gFfHxnBVXSbtVEVbeJDIlb5l6lC0BNiLRtmFw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19014","langCode":"en","question":"bBlBwBqaCAW8LilTIoRAhPSzk2qlrIGZhjNtkB0yd4gAHWyJfrQtOFnl7FC5cyTd","answers":["is","be","would have been","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+Mpb2x55KAQLKHxbbXiR4tLPxAvu5tBHOGmqLxo0n7erzIaS117isV4lkPPUxqpUrWseTxZfPRlZcJbYI4YQ9YZdsZq8QRnbUbTA1ih5Qid4zP6pcSdgq4BeajVuID5QMjgta/SMFm7mqS6lQahAK2by8tzz5KnAWLsw99ZQGbwP+hHnQ0FgG86wqIbX0srliAJqH/r3A/5z+7NNKG5yB/Cxf6ytvvapq5PXIXmTp/VcAuFTRpt0oky60jQs5TE/MwelhbxGK54q2EfeM+IEWjL771pI3fDnPfHnnj5wrxP28xBWeVPI1JAg/PFDsuIy25Ju8axwW7vPhSmZygdwIb4qC24qKhspO6qNkrrgy2EwGb/RlP8OgsJiRnsCfIUXIIL1S2Wg6EnJbxnax7jZVyDjxVrUXr4L2O3atpxWvgy5ESl0iJOIsV6OB6UQKAVGDwRRFoXIgzFjBWM2Xp5gRa/lwn3Xse0agoKGa5+e3/evr0SU0ybvd4CTljSnjB5cGYWvrJNW/h8NqNADhZNXIH8ujFBbPVxlHPerVM8o0CQ7y1Mg51J79uK/cEKw2YtnRk36hPWZVxpzWaZlgsGQg3G+zah+5iudy90KnnU12HC89aNK0mGdzFoYhL/CG6FVXkzAYgCU+u6QdUyWV6RdHr6/F23qN+BWhJeCWXwicmO"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19015","langCode":"en","question":"LfTIi8tFXk8x8fKdrX0d1q0iVklxFAHv+Q40JCgjY6EqtCeFxelcJMTk3U2AN4Xk","answers":["am","are","were","is"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+Mpb2x55KAQLKHxbbXiR4tLPxAvu5tBHOGmqLxo0n7erzIaS117isV4lkPPUxqpUrWseTxZfPRlZcJbYI4YQ9YZdsZq8QRnbUbTA1ih5Qid4zP6pcSdgq4BeajVuID5QMjgta/SMFm7mqS6lQahAK2by8tzz5KnAWLsw99ZQGbwP+hHnQ0FgG86wqIbX0srliAJqH/r3A/5z+7NNKG5yB/Cxf6ytvvapq5PXIXmTp/VcAuFTRpt0oky60jQs5TE/MwelhbxGK54q2EfeM+IEWjL771pI3fDnPfHnnj5wrxP28xBWeVPI1JAg/PFDsuIy25Ju8axwW7vPhSmZygdwIb4qC24qKhspO6qNkrrgy2EwGb/RlP8OgsJiRnsCfIUXIIL1S2Wg6EnJbxnax7jZVyDjxVrUXr4L2O3atpxWvgy5ESl0iJOIsV6OB6UQKAVGDwRRFoXIgzFjBWM2Xp5gRa/lwn3Xse0agoKGa5+e3/evr0SU0ybvd4CTljSnjB5cGYWvrJNW/h8NqNADhZNXIH8ujFBbPVxlHPerVM8o0CQ7y1Mg51J79uK/cEKw2YtnRk36hPWZVxpzWaZlgsGQg3G+zah+5iudy90KnnU12HC89aNK0mGdzFoYhL/CG6FVXkzAYgCU+u6QdUyWV6RdHr6/F23qN+BWhJeCWXwicmO"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19016","langCode":"en","question":"+mXAEvAyrDc4MF5hSbLOrV9k2w4KUAGDLKURpn6IurQeq9iCqK2go6KwU4E+3cNaA4WydYF/Gjn4IBELBpl8NA\u003d\u003d","answers":["visits","visit","were visit","were to visit"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18TVkt2eNuYilO3+NSqMYoTV6BheuKhhiyd+pyMjarCtMCTOrWR5VaobmncV6l9SoTCm1ottIfVBCyOQ8v30AMymFg4y9W4zJNgMmrOGduQyIDeQqiFsTynOo7jGMXcw1s0nbBBNKs9M7GP09F8SIqXRu2mqwbssQFGdG86LMj/gjg0luJyXEruH+v2iBkJrr4MB1VeoqLJWDvvlYR49zLSMrRF0VJUlheT76RUF1xy/6C97UvoC3/jYU8HuObDhmiWV7VJQoEIa4CweYysgpFanVHG7sy3BFIzdXNToBwSesAGy9L2TJ6AREGNgNFUNrchxOEXa3wEh2u5HGd48z3HpQzkLs1MtosmyqPX2kvQvi+VumZlJjOZwGd+C0IN5aPyihu0vYL/LH92CVHXQIdtWSkrUGC71ADsBusKfSaMR0n8J9Mri88kxqWWxRIK1RXo09QIBh61nLH1EZJn75pVMaKeRCbT7RhXzBz7Tij5Tkc19KiCXlErb0/9LfMDTYArCfoDOA0wMqKvysttcD93y3So8qSxc6p+twwcv6D0hoeSfq4GcGx2LX5tw5Yr7LMD2ll6knjKxR7q4ZxPQ7bIZCyA7JMJkH+q/wPH2dVedUfLxJgkr7sdBWCaHxpSDJSCymtxoh55yb7Vg8JWnAfYhNye4I4zXkUarT1ve2l7xQPyQ17Jh8Gm8wRBLgCL/54RvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19017","langCode":"en","question":"lLLTIdc+XSC/IOJjY8WZJwLyj0AB0XOeal6Rcsv6Ivhb4FWE/dtQrA8WcnVWufhJLot9RGptcD1/uh6Xlu8SSA\u003d\u003d","answers":["will look","look","would look","would have looked"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2yp4+QGfeM0B4wqJ+rAizJAYENwcNb1zfz1h3EGkNo7Dt5VfZ7xmiggUg6b+DSiR59wLij1trEZzRfm1/eQ0U/ETHFZAv4za0mLSCiiH7ftseDBqOYdXvO+HXI6qvAhaDc76cYInpdXKu11cYSavOGhC90DTgNXY/WfKnYY7T0/Y118IlDmGyjKsnF2GrK9qFp1ZwbYh9eamSYeEVJRqoBEmdoygpOG4uXOsSAgNNMX7B/t5vIMhRcMLZGiKVTmIvk//agENvoR0z+LTmUvWb6zu8Z79BuwQTGGMuex0DshdGJ8KKEnkd+GBRMn24PkPoS4bXFAaolvEB073EwjWgb6xvs2ofuYrncvdCp51NdhwvPWjStJhncxaGIS/whuhVV5MwGIAlPrukHVMllekXR6+vxdt6jfgVoSXgll8InJjg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19018","langCode":"en","question":"oiqoXLu1PUp/78oR7xaog/gDTTbePEjOCmQwcysD4MdFNFhQnIiENuka6kV7sp9TVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["take","would have taken","will take","took"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2xBjko95BUv/C/LyK9N08fuAeDg57nGOPLczi0N3lgiURridnhDBn7nBCUEfQ5cQu3UAlY9NQgLYS2T+8z9pPa2LYFPrr07j6zZsSqyUhMDc/Xb3tQjCHGdE/o/sqP9fP0n/zDD0K5fos2Cci2sWntbcYnbuaBuQJDe7Zrc+n0UHgo30f6hI9HJhZbS1EXKofHPosarG/GLsaBjfeLvh6wSkgaKP0MwqBuUjXU9CEGlKiYYngawwM1L6Mrd87iyj/zhnuDjKXW0i3+EZBZwwVY3C7zq5ixqYey6xBitKpl0ge1RaiOdEIgNM8l5hiiVQVyDEdV3Q8rWP6XyNxWg545qtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19019","langCode":"en","question":"ojRBzO9CMZtVx8ZrYYx2SG4pfDfjRFPImdsA0U6Kg2XnbKMBoAACX0sYwQZu6W9K","answers":["met","would have met","meet","will meet"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2xBjko95BUv/C/LyK9N08fuAeDg57nGOPLczi0N3lgiURridnhDBn7nBCUEfQ5cQu3UAlY9NQgLYS2T+8z9pPa2LYFPrr07j6zZsSqyUhMDc/Xb3tQjCHGdE/o/sqP9fP0n/zDD0K5fos2Cci2sWntbcYnbuaBuQJDe7Zrc+n0UHgo30f6hI9HJhZbS1EXKofHPosarG/GLsaBjfeLvh6wSkgaKP0MwqBuUjXU9CEGlKsF8kYdf0tQ9JT0BzRfbzjXhnuDjKXW0i3+EZBZwwVY3C7zq5ixqYey6xBitKpl0ge1RaiOdEIgNM8l5hiiVQVyDEdV3Q8rWP6XyNxWg545qtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19020","langCode":"en","question":"JyTtdu8I2PoE/2mG2Mui8PJbI2dBMY56AkEwUdZVfQp7aOeEENpm4OW+cFNaigB2","answers":["could have contacted","contact","will contact","have contacted"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11IiIba9bynkMItVdPidQghwsjOaeBl/M2Ka7U9zv5aJ/b7tAsub0nw/KVeJLNOw3Wv2WyZ+VIi+72mTsaKHbHh0D/GjntN1FZh2JqMwxJEB9uCy1x/YNYBvJYDq7LA3mADjT5ag9IT3ffpJNU4mIwCOoz1jup3//lqZhjO36zYOmIcxoeVMTY3YY3EaQU7eFbNBnOSQU/tSKsUaKkgn5xLEmvnTRHbK56xOfmPf4utZtJajEU9xlX2huE9nXue4b/zR1rqen31HB3AAJLaXY6Lkqxe+zorDKPkX0T+/wTwaW7CqN5VZqbv4NQEaS8dMnxPZid7k79Km6/HZNuEDM9Lsvxwzi+kbrWHOSRGEeig3XS+FIhejPQfpwRYh8432LMz9B3JF3f0dCIAFd2z4nkpZSvShrHfPfe3wwZ+XOCp7JBMzF7n+qTTlmhAzv9bZmxMVDnedALxtgqIZeqS5kMOEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19021","langCode":"en","question":"fx1frURI2jue12/4WXk8K6/JFQlH2SRwJxwGu6Lel5+SvhqmiRRuhu597xH4AKJdkGXSpDc5KN/EHJmzAYgfqHGw/tnWInEmhbURjT6rS9VUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["will miss","missed","might have missed","miss"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17O+alozBySXjVwwr6jh/SVVjZycfFyxOGKdp0GdkaheXTtgYy1/1/vY54QJzsohV1h/fINE1WAyh9XdhtjiNK5iML57Bjao4LTkv2x9QU3oq9hTnh3MhxuafE47qosiEmWmsjSnovuV6IFIW0tDSKAtbceeaql3NwN0VlMS7Ee29DgKNkaNB37c7Vw3855UKjwknep2tnhI0n7TZ+cQITAkbSWNVzOYZnS2S90q5pYaicRQ8STy3Db19RF46Yk2OD+aJrqPAd9NsCgm3w7gDS3/AnhWUHZduDcZDAJHPbiqR6S3eMrr4R/qRZ3Ta1VH8CLZLNO6gfwzcRFUzi/T8ZtWRpx7t66lq+w2ZiA0GvwHxsYks6Tq+lJjtcNTNeJohMb7NqH7mK53L3QqedTXYcJ9LiHvCPbDkAUJ3SY2DwVzsEKsm3gFS5vV1rt8AikbnNH3d0SC5L83/2nanithMqM\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19022","langCode":"en","question":"K8IVui4Pl6eWDCj/Yw4Jt5y4sWdSxF4DnCynkgD74DhRzysN0pw6/RYal4U7kv0wuXMpj5VMBkdT7F0/xGtjrg\u003d\u003d","answers":["pass","would have passed","passed","will pass"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2xHQqcnHqXLUoq1NFsoVoljXTtgYy1/1/vY54QJzsohV1h/fINE1WAyh9XdhtjiNK5iML57Bjao4LTkv2x9QU3oq9hTnh3MhxuafE47qosiEmWmsjSnovuV6IFIW0tDSKAtbceeaql3NwN0VlMS7Ee29DgKNkaNB37c7Vw3855UKjwknep2tnhI0n7TZ+cQITAkbSWNVzOYZnS2S90q5pYaicRQ8STy3Db19RF46Yk2ODG+k1ieeH82scW2ymBGJ9+2kBbMKnAQUIs1iH9Xq+DbnwDfk6h1UcwyOLShFmxQ7ZklAEVs/mSxoBoLxTYnJIqjuHa3eeQ2Tudnf2eNdzt485vFKBWmo0BMxCdEBHTbeQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19023","langCode":"en","question":"FhN/YavJN2XjOwwxCTlbD5NFMRMHNereF/IhQDc4Jsbrfc68ktWCpq8x3VRUfBbWVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["will be","is being","is","would have been"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2yOBiMvHVxYq45sCdOXwxYtVx8VjH7ggwmtWHzj/8Xzdia0ukMBax05k9DbVFmZ4XWQXXFVfzfy8iF8/CjE7n/Q8HbHRANJunfJf4i/tACN1QmcJfQ8ekd95lS62JBZloIWvq9Z3QcMsbEodAZXhp6z3rg02HgWEdnPdotwneVY4jOeo0P9xl5JuQX8ipaAuCnJb4TrcB8NJXSfrTjLTRUBf7zrgQ4ZkBWsRDq5s6MTw3+W31xjwwLhwjtPx91eoGrM/QdyRd39HQiABXds+J5KWUr0oax3z33t8MGflzgqeyQTMxe5/qk05ZoQM7/W2ZsTFQ53nQC8bYKiGXqkuZDDhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19024","langCode":"en","question":"MlT1v9OV8SvWY9Ox4UBxgAFqRCBOWRC24rtOzdVqQEsaQ3qggS/cexwNdMovX4cXELVQuBxn+NamUO7rGHY2T8ky5qraphZ1YPl1L9jVJSM\u003d","answers":["will know","know","should know","wouldn’t have known"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16Hc1/snUWOEI54IXjwO6z6MNFHW3stoRKmX9WmKbjv/QpRzQATPBtAad4g2r/Km89CacScqLqznQ7uWJTIIoym3ODiL/tln9kSP6WUSwDv/1NZQhEZpfPyil8CpSgzz3WwvqYanX89ECCw+eexyb2fJOi2ICHbEUrafKYrB4XQR7KqwiLEQhz6So97l8D5lhz2l+guugyiUu4UNbhBNqdjZvSAZuyvk2rv2vvvkEGjhNHCvqx9nsPcft87n5yAh5uFptipDzJ97Rq6ETMFpZXIw9ks9Rk5uYq1xtsdD1v01p9ZntR3h79KjWAt8xexzJS16qJs7AQ/RTdMMarcqwoY5uBr6WZku3luWJA0/nb0J6mdajVS/5uXqk4ee3AOXAw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19025","langCode":"en","question":"vWMMR3uytgKhgAlslqKAsQIA8Z1uv3OFKNf0l9Vk5+7U5OqQkr3r0rLjCK5iAaxp","answers":["fine","could fine","would have fined","would fine"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12dZlSIVw4oJ9xEDJFccz42EAisQumLozlq3cnPAbtmVzV7PfywaMAVPlG32Tn7UFPCNE3TLmbyYUs0A+R4CvlcYnANK+/q6fUSy80WOcCGGUub3Px0DmKbUxL5SX5P/3CbkjkKiXUbCv6qIqlYuE1C0+h9YTjCxWNGBhuT6RMNWkWltHHaKLpu/xeWBBrQZGb/Ij/WxxoLvYHfoP+ptzF6JYq9KY7jRYAKpDJyhqZPHJqvUXoraLDzkfIpVaykZJ3FuaEAY64faddLQMkQguam27mY4HX60Od6otvw+6UzdsYQa42JS1NZdHggjDrBQ67NMume0pZxLgXiTweBw9woiyOO+3wj3pV4pCSaWS6vUp0M0cRzYKfrl1zkkyUrl5zaAhWFa4B8zafKh5BS3h6VVodhpqZseSYkvdZRv/qNSUBhqXCwv1/wv+1aqBH9/blzrkJDgLE2+bTiacz7Gv0qo5Mg/7JojbYKkis6UHcV4J8cbLHlkAOCbiIfREd0V2jaFg0XDuscI5gjqSqgiRcPs7v9bKrqy3s/3Au+eF+SLg4duPZewu4kwARG+0tB7BK7CxSobi4Vbj5Ec5swub9I\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19026","langCode":"en","question":"B8PhyHRLwW9a00E43jJfxy5C2I9qKCWjvWEbPRzkgI/ZCNdlB1GGjTmWVv2wJt94PyYBBgtLmmt0/liG7j7lbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["eat","would eat","could have eaten","would have eaten"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yQALtNgDlCi1471QocA5v8y5HjiYqdhx87VBsoHMnhgakW2ndaN2phR9dZbQcGIgq1rjGbvpr/97lSrYNOIg3lWCRMhPetR5q3aObOekx5IK0oMRNi2smn2vSD3UHqpA0XhiTLcK031iFehIrqOFvalQxboG9KQEkQ0ZSWXs9Tyu680dx8Ab3BBJ0/xcJt1oaXHq9APrGvi+He3f6wi2/RjCEWSe1wf2RyZLUMjyunkLnsgEQOXw3AhJ9IZHgCZt3iDNPps4FXIEvDJZCajL5clH7dZ057XSrzyGpIPujxDLXSeSnIspySwOPS08SyB+a9XEP2fXDr/k4nzqEM81qVCHk5uaJ/4YNXUnK2UNdYCqOTIP+yaI22CpIrOlB3FeJsu6ge2Lwob0jiELquCGizGaa4S9NpWNVYERKJfu4BWRO2b1eUtjOqNq8BvuKOIMXDLqd58qrlN0aL3Kjih1j/1rBvgrj07/xS4hJ3aJOyd7pHzgBhKcP3hyu0S4T4MxHHgOPOkUHcC8ZlxmQvfq2OnvcO+rY3CHgmeFu2yI0fTWgpHXx1DFB7evSmhgHp1gveUm4mXm5R9jvbYHaq+F90\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19027","langCode":"en","question":"XTxeTJDHe2fVlsopc3RjoH0gwEBe1GjKkBP6/6Nnd598yhu6T90ZJcDSntoATr8aA1tOesVWG4whUfJTUzWY530pGuZlA+jrBbCOez4JSPBlICir6M1AugVtaKbSba6mHu/WZ4gnmZVEmOlsTbfCZg\u003d\u003d","answers":["should have let","would have let","would let","let"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wDPNj5JkvoznHatF27oMLMy5HjiYqdhx87VBsoHMnhgakW2ndaN2phR9dZbQcGIgq1rjGbvpr/97lSrYNOIg3lWCRMhPetR5q3aObOekx5IK0oMRNi2smn2vSD3UHqpA0XhiTLcK031iFehIrqOFvalQxboG9KQEkQ0ZSWXs9Tyu680dx8Ab3BBJ0/xcJt1oaXHq9APrGvi+He3f6wi2/RjCEWSe1wf2RyZLUMjyunkLnsgEQOXw3AhJ9IZHgCZt3iDNPps4FXIEvDJZCajL5clH7dZ057XSrzyGpIPujxDLXSeSnIspySwOPS08SyB+a9XEP2fXDr/k4nzqEM81qVCHk5uaJ/4YNXUnK2UNdYCqOTIP+yaI22CpIrOlB3FeJsu6ge2Lwob0jiELquCGizGaa4S9NpWNVYERKJfu4BWRO2b1eUtjOqNq8BvuKOIMXDLqd58qrlN0aL3Kjih1j/1rBvgrj07/xS4hJ3aJOyd7pHzgBhKcP3hyu0S4T4MxHHgOPOkUHcC8ZlxmQvfq2OnvcO+rY3CHgmeFu2yI0fTWgpHXx1DFB7evSmhgHp1gveUm4mXm5R9jvbYHaq+F90\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19028","langCode":"en","question":"saooUzPSXuzzRjmNDzW4V5pnBEZiGH3d0EbezqdCprt8cCKCw6XliSAIOY5ddHQ+NQ0D7WGPeagcVAnToeV8IQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["would grow","is growing","should grow","are growing"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17uNUKqh/8PoCdpi4VvxJvh73zSD1lStvOuNNLRUMLxPxbSOwm0yyMU5pu5tHKthzobk4YbKzqrOhmE7oI8RappqJJPidqEoyXjXvSV7sN/eCtEytPgrqbjQpymD5MqFmRZdqoLJAnuG82ajBFkL/2c4SYJQJpnnddSQ2t5e5g+qmt4FMm3Y/XydP7KJlwSQGDqEfxwphBafNmD3x68jHJz4Zdo73OkN325AtUOuLLrWXWCyhSUxrv4ZxnlQ9C/KRWoCmjbH8TLY4ZlktOUxuCedCzavStyeGi7yfR7IO9ABRHh0n9FfhrpWJnal8te7WohcyoXKK3WaIW2LQdgbjVBCALrZ5ikRgHigSdlE+r3A+MM0pA26hPSdZhy0Qq7+C70iThasJngWtdstj8QkkihaQSVXQZBFsEJWTkXFygFh+EDLO1dqudCQ907Cli6Wx0Sfs2Q9T4Sk/9wPmV08W+VLuubvi+T6YZiDvneBRFazAUWlOnaCLigMaoOX2JJpMIy+cfbdHZfLKQnobxWkEXpWyEEgYIHpVNZsHGj3lQppeBGdFkh0kEa61XALavmfNySTsfglQOPiBovcUM+YRI2zTsKVePI0ntfkN0S8QevA"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19029","langCode":"en","question":"gsU0vc0UYonnO22dUneDI58FH24ux7B2O5AzokNMYUQcVlFolorNcVb51LyfBHuq/MJFjQ5FwTaCZqwQ8eJM2YRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["would have gone","could have gone","went","go"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19tM0nmw56sjXML0MvYxb+mEAisQumLozlq3cnPAbtmVzV7PfywaMAVPlG32Tn7UFPCNE3TLmbyYUs0A+R4CvlcYnANK+/q6fUSy80WOcCGGUub3Px0DmKbUxL5SX5P/3CbkjkKiXUbCv6qIqlYuE1C0+h9YTjCxWNGBhuT6RMNWkWltHHaKLpu/xeWBBrQZGb/Ij/WxxoLvYHfoP+ptzF6JYq9KY7jRYAKpDJyhqZPHJqvUXoraLDzkfIpVaykZJ3FuaEAY64faddLQMkQguam27mY4HX60Od6otvw+6UzdsYQa42JS1NZdHggjDrBQ67NMume0pZxLgXiTweBw9woiyOO+3wj3pV4pCSaWS6vUp0M0cRzYKfrl1zkkyUrl5zaAhWFa4B8zafKh5BS3h6VVodhpqZseSYkvdZRv/qNSUBhqXCwv1/wv+1aqBH9/blzrkJDgLE2+bTiacz7Gv0qo5Mg/7JojbYKkis6UHcV4J8cbLHlkAOCbiIfREd0V2jaFg0XDuscI5gjqSqgiRcPs7v9bKrqy3s/3Au+eF+SLg4duPZewu4kwARG+0tB7BK7CxSobi4Vbj5Ec5swub9I\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19030","langCode":"en","question":"DXedg4sHb1RI+Sg6dwvm0cA2MDpFrDiwryMoimYc4gMHrLn2U7Y0P6q9Nuu/NLM4fIQunqMw7V1ijpPqIQ1D+A\u003d\u003d","answers":["could have been","would not be","be","will be"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+qBekwn2OxNE7/931lzNx1q93xcc1whlM803FNrG3l65OU9LWLe4AQnvqmURnWnUbbuZjgdfrQ53qi2/D7pTN078/mf9dj1ZcG1g8zZvvFbi2MHBysAsCrxjxvrIaxumqtgF1jVh+PK8l3RE8CkEdpLaOyeUAg18AVypyheq6ojlZt7dM45P62fMCcUbLajQNlsE0LLHxbfFyMHo42gwQsbZ6Ije8Fb7AP1yyvoaG6dPphKSWiFBoJcJSb/7UCkqyhxGKOGK+J9WLSU8egUuQLqZ42GtlMV2/kOGH/MSAscuUjhTUWmtztyRs5J5+HHChZD0lUpEemYqNLX4GRjLX7aYaP1ot7Pguoq+7HXwkS28CWCtxs1v3G129A4YZcO0g1qwJIYkzTR1ASQbTovg/Yxp41PLYUWaVpHw3UmnJGbu3dQK8dX+7chOTdOqlLjN2v389P3gNW2johwTIDmb5WWWUDHhdkpjGV1s78GJ4NaubF3rMaFRM6A8JlsWD+ckVKTeIAfCV9PFW35XyCBOQmFERpb3KoEBwVGkz7PHML3"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19031","langCode":"en","question":"x7PsKkJPCU8+FwiC802BGvB1f7DTy6u3nzb6s5C1cLkcoE43gJC6/wP3IXPGNhMjCHVDwHmDQMTm5nT2w2yD8HHc3Q362e3V8/S5+qqH3Sw\u003d","answers":["would go","will go","could have gone","go"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+qBekwn2OxNE7/931lzNx1q93xcc1whlM803FNrG3l65OU9LWLe4AQnvqmURnWnUbbuZjgdfrQ53qi2/D7pTN078/mf9dj1ZcG1g8zZvvFbi2MHBysAsCrxjxvrIaxumqtgF1jVh+PK8l3RE8CkEdpLaOyeUAg18AVypyheq6ojlZt7dM45P62fMCcUbLajQNlsE0LLHxbfFyMHo42gwQsbZ6Ije8Fb7AP1yyvoaG6dPphKSWiFBoJcJSb/7UCkqyhxGKOGK+J9WLSU8egUuQLqZ42GtlMV2/kOGH/MSAscuUjhTUWmtztyRs5J5+HHChZD0lUpEemYqNLX4GRjLX7aYaP1ot7Pguoq+7HXwkS28CWCtxs1v3G129A4YZcO0g1qwJIYkzTR1ASQbTovg/Yxp41PLYUWaVpHw3UmnJGbu3dQK8dX+7chOTdOqlLjN2v389P3gNW2johwTIDmb5WWWUDHhdkpjGV1s78GJ4NaubF3rMaFRM6A8JlsWD+ckVKTeIAfCV9PFW35XyCBOQmFERpb3KoEBwVGkz7PHML3"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19032","langCode":"en","question":"KZEXweef+WL3SJxsC0Oj8nx+jAASPDcnUFadjVlhjoy/HqJsDclei4GO+lJ2i4NjfIQunqMw7V1ijpPqIQ1D+A\u003d\u003d","answers":["will be","be","would be","would have been"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+qBekwn2OxNE7/931lzNx2clFVDzfZj980s75rCHSjtg28xg0LBugUFA6A5dzxY+pn1ICPjFkXu0lnsXvKKoa6NeNm525bhmQugqPGjI6+l0JpxJyourOdDu5YlMgijKe02vcLtgb4GAeN+K/386EZl4XPgKiBtqERdDZvZELKWAnaa5lNdA49nDPFUuKKmsOdrXQcL2aTzBqKyQ0kNDR6vqexaEuFemPJt/wV/ohfDrXwOtX3n3LGA57o0300hyjIX9SXjpl0IJXwE3iHc8brBEpabROS97WaJ7vRYbXiqG8zl9TmxBE6pd1Kicmtg6PTCM+r9HObnOD//x86Ani6LYwcHKwCwKvGPG+shrG6aphozaqHBPLrV2AFjyCbvT89dOSg19ozgUg7Usy2zFf2s6SQrIpEzOAFVEtHXkst6SfnUQ+cfy92vER05lcS41yXGav3wUVUzSDQ2KnFjXbdxw7jNyFQoTFq+DiAe/SM7dhumMFXjdCVJqGLtMa12pjb5zTD43D11RLXkVVlANRjvgk59uO0cWTfZsNrWGq1a"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19033","langCode":"en","question":"s6dK2VgEDuDBznvDeeVarom++CZJ/Kj+28NBNXir/gJ1wGDQhTLWcL7Uyc9c/8IAyM6FOR5WzgdW5GPFZinlw8kOVh+UWnIfBHrgOhW+oiU\u003d","answers":["had bumped","should bump","could bump","bumped"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zaWElA3vxzcbryUSkU2DvfrKdwCiPlwylPONPNv5nR8WlTogBKakaqWzZuAGLFQbrYFSe0iqsTBmFvOBq5O9s8ygzYgMMf/gZ0asxY2aqcaACV/+yqyCo0bIMfw7rDpR5FvdGd45q9VFyNqFVQYh8wmSWH56Uz7xq+V1gbNI0g2q+JF7bqKGLtcKbFy94OlL8bxUFAt66R0sddT6YJ7Cc15EtF1wwzikS8okA9mwq3f9AArK8bmjp0Ajv0RKIITP6JncUQBtwfANwk30pOHPHEGlcWj+YiIM3STGcViDB2z"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19034","langCode":"en","question":"DzyBzwF0Q4ReWDs4BYDQbWgq+aekaunj9O3w9dZaVnLARDyxzQZbu+eCN3MDKcvtLkyUtawlMjfZBROejgewB1NOuH6Z0q75iDgL9dmt1H6nRZCmM/kvSi+zzpKxeS7p7PhayR70kqVSCEcrU6GKmQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["should ever find","found","had found","could ever find"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zaWElA3vxzcbryUSkU2DvcpmeHWmJhO9kYwoes3lAXOFuud353qbKMW6/8mTeRhZpf3yIKxOckCWBcQWILgJjNqPmWbH4lr9TwK52Ii2VQB9rqHYo4QlZtb4Ip+QCvItbueOUCBrecCOUtC7AA7EmVoegP1jKI5wHsRDgfnYrqGE7VxRpN8cFrjYlb/nZISe6e5YxYQLcKqHlNcW+2MFkHSSZlw9sdFgKpvMtZ33kOOrIwVhfttUZ8W5KEZMOK+3g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19035","langCode":"en","question":"U+TNTH05Q+KXIlyPJ65Zd4JG75a5ScDhVQ5l3cA6mWB+2mZ7+BW471jVh/mkToVpNjFisnLdzo5D5WvczZ+flIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["could meet","will meet","met","had met"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x177RjpZjU4TJ9p+DDYaBKcQ5yPkoz8oHsRrZ4ibMNpUvo1HNXV1/PpzVprMSRZ1UEhTBlRs5mt/9alYqfc2ZVdmXf0lNT/P+/j9Ouvnu5nXuUWv5Pdu5App/C3uxFUhMoU0rv80GfCmmOqqJL+2s9Mft53EIxbRIGJwCTg1eIQdQ9H7qrCitnMv6pKEvrJ0s/VjgEC4PhDp9RxNuwQFfHRNnpWou3EPvaSFnByEBkKDDS++nXxz+HIh0BqT7raI3D9zHkcP2PyMHuuieSPmXZX5G2yDPXBbi7ohRqrQy3nqe"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19036","langCode":"en","question":"zwuEfcbjAehQ+hJmqXA+kwonB/eazuWvKF4+qE++0xBk28RvyzQjBGEgq7dhxfa/kSwjNuPz9tgBDe04QqquiQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["would all stop","could all stop","stopped","had stopped"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19D0tA9m+tKXcJEGoR1hM2wH35mRCDJlX9Rka3/XWFErMoM2IDDH/4GdGrMWNmqnGgAlf/sqsgqNGyDH8O6w6UeRb3RneOavVRcjahVUGIfMEPoAeDHEsMbX/AtqbtaN0Hu+oSKxrITzpRgvIV4TTTkxP4/sr7JVfNPGUQJzLb3bkIHPIYVuira16L3F7ng6HCzXHoygBpKe0N9Jaztirw7whEpZTjFNkB3si7H6Ho67whXDMCfzmtYxz4zBRK2nkqXAaYAIxbVV8ZUSQfnKpJWSBduxslZuBV/A9CJdMd4y4x6mh2isVQSFfgzuGnDdbg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19037","langCode":"en","question":"zGCFGOjdw5vD2yu+zSft6XRyCzub8c3A/SE08jhyjX+5sJKWXJAbjdu65QoYFYXFX8y9lLBB0szR8Afw5D54rw\u003d\u003d","answers":["will make","could make","had made","made"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x177RjpZjU4TJ9p+DDYaBKcRyCx5q/AfI11Fmq3TyaL8iv8sO0pJCKNFyjjzggO+TT9Ge/4jyzG1sEjHDjz/wFleaaUgxbvA5RUEjy+FaJiyuveGkmhSD0PO3/OEEKw9w+GTRGfb2O8slKf2lXCn6hvKjUc1dXX8+nNWmsxJFnVQSFMGVGzma3/1qVip9zZlV2Zd/SU1P8/7+P066+e7mde5Ra/k927kCmn8Le7EVSEyhTSu/zQZ8KaY6qokv7az0x+3ncQjFtEgYnAJODV4hB1D0fuqsKK2cy/qkoS+snSz9WOAQLg+EOn1HE27BAV8dE2elai7cQ+9pIWcHIQGQoMNL76dfHP4ciHQGpPutojcP3MeRw/Y/Iwe66J5I+ZdlfkbbIM9cFuLuiFGqtDLeep4\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19038","langCode":"en","question":"tU8motCN2FzWXBh2cjiE6qyrDXGXSt5WvkOUI2dwB/pf2RYp6NJdq1XxI1G5rZ8D","answers":["am","were","is","be"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+Mpb2x55KAQLKHxbbXiR4sFiQe9bHhWYXkB/mB9T0v6fdBF+gD82aZD/teUgqUDTK8yGktde4rFeJZDz1MaqVLS+ksHFyEU763hHNlDysPagmxWZRNtZFNhJhdvItDtK6bgo55/xwONjzaUvbH6xi7V57sl7x+pArVEx1s9HiVvpszKaU34V4VvbJXlFa4TPMM4Q+AMpNsDW/Mq1itgWH0dD/njOLZklFwpqEg6aO4LoHWvcxdTP74tt8oTi9NN5JUAvBs+NUP+wbB/DLOLPsW+eAe/DCBSpby9mf0EiH8iHttVIihg928ncLh7AYP3BflGrI8fh4Ltm9EsIc7vTwyrRK7rcYS4xLJADyfLB2Hg"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19039","langCode":"en","question":"2IviABZqDvnVNGwZMngR3yZTL5k968bXmEl7npO1doqLjGJyLN1zW2LzKJZfCpYcWsm8/aGekcP6S35iUxxQKQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["are","was","were","had"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xcXlYR8gJfbpXqccALXvHIvJqqPpWW6soZH3zXSnqAfHh4EqLFozTPCeMn4540Gd9TWUIRGaXz8opfAqUoM8928VkCC/E9FfTgN4GnrLXX1Ho90F5zFFQ0O7x1ZdmWtiP2g12wjZKfuImD093glQSg4KIFtZw8zjk7VrFWKBn+BJkPwZzSKaBd2bwR6pjTnkEJQ5SWCaRlqHXfUGEWFv2SgaPJzgd2V0EGdwJ+nbHzcO5uC/pX7wPhwcMSA0xk3zPU804wdHABkG8LKFd14XUct4Zn1DvOk45RnyBBi4+KTKkDmoYBBSA5bvjUNh/kYOjeR8VPCAnIORKTtRKQkxVmdvciDMRVs01YKfL5nKU+gOWQ8egcLtJe6lTio3ea3ng\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19040","langCode":"en","question":"s89cmCcy36iHZYo2oSYDS1nHSDGxt4k1EVcYRx4eDW4wN/SvYdwIgbtf67wvcQdq","answers":["had","is","were","should"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xcXlYR8gJfbpXqccALXvHIvJqqPpWW6soZH3zXSnqAfnfM4OznuyCbqax0qzhx61u+khEa7tCN8HI20ufBhTG68VkCC/E9FfTgN4GnrLXX1Ho90F5zFFQ0O7x1ZdmWtiAcpDxuSNs4jauGQiKfD4G/V57sl7x+pArVEx1s9HiVvpszKaU34V4VvbJXlFa4TPP+1/8PiFFaReDANvuFeTBCyxTywqrLZKOaTW/bY2VTVVyFN3xZAq5owcoUTR2lxVhiGSWrNE4HX8xOg9ITJ0OUzSpqKKqsMsxKXRjOYDO+bkSR/JjkvyyKTG8ETDa9TTpIIEmdZZOJyHkU8QBqQ313Ypd0ut6D6nkzGVkZCM8Hr4x6mh2isVQSFfgzuGnDdbg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19041","langCode":"en","question":"OTmUZL7vxl1USCthiChbWcllQFlVLSm5TCf5Wlx9PUFB7s4oJ4rCeZOkYsg2yZdp3NTbZtWoh3Nt8WYXiJxwxl0ioYFk1fz3XIXRBDNA/AQ\u003d","answers":["are","was","had","were"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xcXlYR8gJfbpXqccALXvHIvJqqPpWW6soZH3zXSnqAfHh4EqLFozTPCeMn4540Gd9TWUIRGaXz8opfAqUoM8928VkCC/E9FfTgN4GnrLXX1Ho90F5zFFQ0O7x1ZdmWtiP2g12wjZKfuImD093glQSg4KIFtZw8zjk7VrFWKBn+BJkPwZzSKaBd2bwR6pjTnkEJQ5SWCaRlqHXfUGEWFv2SgaPJzgd2V0EGdwJ+nbHzcO5uC/pX7wPhwcMSA0xk3zPU804wdHABkG8LKFd14XUct4Zn1DvOk45RnyBBi4+KTKkDmoYBBSA5bvjUNh/kYOjeR8VPCAnIORKTtRKQkxVmdvciDMRVs01YKfL5nKU+gPXJYt6VNbz9nzsSzifdeVg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19042","langCode":"en","question":"bFvx9tpMg0YIaiN3EY8Od1ifaQ/Jynp6XsMb71yLFFXeS9OqSvS7rpXRULwSCOYC","answers":["will come","would have come","came","would come"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/Rv900h7J8c041bR82ukJuXkI2dICGHmDz2wKhuRv7ByhLly7MmhMSyD1M3Jvj4YDjHf9TDGrPMBufzcpUyvrIjj0/k8dMYsRb9VAqq02GnrEDBhJ8OTkpeI4VXB0VPrEfwMWvhQG2f7VE2lgxIBg0ZM67VNl3gdw0yqLj+SdIw1sYcZmKAlIdQAqZpgiDcrhqyvRf5CkO5/uABMT6H8DMx3CeFO1BZBkqjyBstSqXx"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19043","langCode":"en","question":"+QDvMzPda28jyLGFLXc+77PnsQmcjNkMjvuWlIuPc+NF0IuEIbJ/aNT3V9+eFYmb","answers":["if","unless","only if","but for"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/iUaPbeNdRqAgQq45Xzv48x+yy9NB4xPc7BZc5Qa2ET3RNuO+ycZbDxOgbwaqyop1UIU/Rxf4djI4DfX2yz+QD974VgBghKX4Hzguf3KbvDVIw/jaVtZ440wKqUPvBb3bZ3budgMTolKXYzVMiMJgaIpM2BR7AB8UODvH7nBsxOhv8WoHuFgcnEOtixeJ41Rm84p1imTlpOpOEGoSqc33Sl6xPuFYhoYwF9gAg1qalTdlLwM/lwTHSu5rQb/ytW1fHS3a8ThDa5PKFxXoP1rdkO+neM8mYh+Yy3BLU6jLFG"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19044","langCode":"en","question":"zp41McNxOfG1C6C26fkiQgyt2uEqtCmVLYMomEyPCuZdIqGBZNX891yF0QQzQPwE","answers":["unless","otherwise","as long as","if"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/iUaPbeNdRqAgQq45Xzv48x+yy9NB4xPc7BZc5Qa2ET3RNuO+ycZbDxOgbwaqyop1UIU/Rxf4djI4DfX2yz+QD974VgBghKX4Hzguf3KbvDVIw/jaVtZ440wKqUPvBb3bZ3budgMTolKXYzVMiMJgaIpM2BR7AB8UODvH7nBsxOhv8WoHuFgcnEOtixeJ41RuXAQGpiuuw+p4h4yZaHfKLJpz2iXhK2EoLt+5yPjn5U70xLS6IMPRJhUIFa1++zp3M9G2UvCqNh9bM2jLxtjVHhd9+NOZVNSinJmig03u50U5gCZ4Tcut+CGDDfw2UdcUM/8CTlIGQ10dv+H6mTgNqe3zPOUtEmgk/ntRoF8fhlB9ioZTPjMlmzKwE2IKsVI8g5LYf58HVdc2tePECk35wVqevhdI8OzyHcXSIwSyAdCvmD/UHYktvZMtjxV666PC51fOJDt5dtS0d7yEKv5vKEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19045","langCode":"en","question":"DXWlWTYDieiU8uKrIY3DFJGeC2bLULA2oFwjGfRjT2j33t9M9V66SapbbETTZ4qFkvLxrp5M+xr1cwOZPrT3Prfj9s7slX7DYgwwQptX7k8\u003d","answers":["if","only if","unless","otherwise"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/iUaPbeNdRqAgQq45Xzv48x+yy9NB4xPc7BZc5Qa2ET3RNuO+ycZbDxOgbwaqyop1UIU/Rxf4djI4DfX2yz+QD974VgBghKX4Hzguf3KbvDVIw/jaVtZ440wKqUPvBb3bZ3budgMTolKXYzVMiMJgaIpM2BR7AB8UODvH7nBsxOhv8WoHuFgcnEOtixeJ41RuXAQGpiuuw+p4h4yZaHfKLJpz2iXhK2EoLt+5yPjn5U70xLS6IMPRJhUIFa1++zp8tk68tifarbnmQP5nhHOv9VORjHb4Ax7Zt3oX7WCzyUybNLO3MPk97DWZMWauPWJexNuJm5H2zoX3/r5WLbxycbIKpxfEdwEXDcOUOq1Lg06Rxg5m8yDTBLn5IJUWJUm3xqRTSXki5c4B+/tYkBBsRMR5jDLzcEVkJGF9L/cWxg1jx9r8dkx6HAVllgg39p1jVUSLaQaYOxqZLreZyDP8s\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19046","langCode":"en","question":"aV6lZhqEd4fjCYQzlMq6+V6KufSd9Z8VPPmv91B89RVaxEkofe591pXjxw3+KCamK6y9R4Vq2vGOuGcTYme2PQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["provided that","but for","otherwise","unless"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19N+pz+vZDSeuDts5l+ljXQN5Mt4B20KybhWF67TKzx/8RsEFVdHLP1+MnBVYa5nKyzJtACYwmTBKG1c7U3SfVbQf9D6hUJ2z3ov4sUYy/z93D0lZqmFedQNn9KfU2xUPLD6qPTcRi2wBuHd02feEuanmFb7LyOpuvLfLY1Csrk0cT3An5zTiKIHfNeIwJjeh2qUQz9AZTXOnasDxUBSP19DP/Ak5SBkNdHb/h+pk4Dant8zzlLRJoJP57UaBfH4ZS0NFq9o4Cu2GeuocCp2Em51MG5iemcX0XUC6ZR4s8rkIJ99t7TT42v2+EJcCWHNf6mzn7Eyah52Y+FcF4ZsjGlZpHukH++XQGIMdCE6kdnAuHt9FtjAypeQb+zC6rxMs4ikzYFHsAHxQ4O8fucGzE6G/xage4WBycQ62LF4njVG24rh4t3jmjSLEzfUo3yfwQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19047","langCode":"en","question":"RaZftd0xq1zczuIPoGrSNo4OZ4zDDZYBdXBRs8x73yWx3gMnoKMyugNABcqBKxMAUuZsi7ArckZJbn77P+GJ0A\u003d\u003d","answers":["as long as","but for","otherwise","if"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1ztqL69Smaz9/TQMimU0GQ8nGJUtG/F7o5YyvkMzOwTZ0JpxJyourOdDu5YlMgijKfviLy/AXPqsRARPoMbk7aIGG3vIyk6JDP2WSmMWbQsfT0w+PliBeleHVIjalJLKKObOWcfSx9F5Zav2AAwTFli8eHE8SHc3fLTQpm0wtXj/+VoS0pnR1+W7zHI7GoYE620+7PGDPLlkwH0/+JV0KTHhd9+NOZVNSinJmig03u508toEuOeNbGpclPVb0PAzakO85tu7BksZxjAmgoEBOtAErmtRMcRZZqvkl1iKNvi8W7hYCH73PpZ6xCyWnwVIozLs09aVzQdJI8MITeZd8oAb+8BjE0wvUPa6xOzsMMNqhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19048","langCode":"en","question":"ZxILORlQCzSJyHcMeH0dP89dGm9Dz9zuOXp526ecHNxa/aDmxNfZlfcSYNkmKluW2r5A+5i3toRivS+Fkexsww\u003d\u003d","answers":["otherwise","unless","only if","if"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1x1oZAgOe4c8S4ta6kyUX2VJB6pAfcr2Iy1UpOaCSdtsW6YtCin7iQtjedVH1PzElfviLy/AXPqsRARPoMbk7aIGG3vIyk6JDP2WSmMWbQsfT0w+PliBeleHVIjalJLKKObOWcfSx9F5Zav2AAwTFlgonjihi7bZuP+fOJpglSEZRsAqJ19ihDjK+DgMz6HerTGplLLUY6luVXL/jC3fEWyxdqrgCw68chRf5BdUVP8Rbcu6XU/Is6Ab+NCWJWLpgjGj2LH3x4UPKOUQUDrMV2uIpM2BR7AB8UODvH7nBsxOhv8WoHuFgcnEOtixeJ41RjrD+QetNCP+DdRAu4kQNJ0\u003d"},{"topicId":"19","id":"19049","langCode":"en","question":"2tfOBSKnamNvdgxky6PM+YqLBZH/WuUHJzoSClEOZI5SLcA0bT/y7+E+CGzV1DsDyX3Y5pbSzPiYMzsyQZZXiQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["as long as","otherwise","unless","but for"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1127MyNcmf9r4+J2P7MPHokRNMadn6Amum00Uoa3MHB7xbSOwm0yyMU5pu5tHKthzjjHf9TDGrPMBufzcpUyvrIjj0/k8dMYsRb9VAqq02GnrEDBhJ8OTkpeI4VXB0VPrEfwMWvhQG2f7VE2lgxIBg2EzkGlyjceEhFacyWtAdpiVTkYx2+AMe2bd6F+1gs8lMmzSztzD5Pew1mTFmrj1iXsTbiZuR9s6F9/6+Vi28cnGyCqcXxHcBFw3DlDqtS4NKkRJiKtGKyt8SWZ5jHP30g2KWBzrGYYnuOxcBQJzXv43qQ9h6CNLYtihP9FSHsMbwckPGYoBOyyWgIGDcWupK23rRDX8GB3MLjXYAjv3kd5V/VTPX1np8wS98Npc2IjTyOmr4yPrh/XhY7wuDqJfH/ixe2YObVCaR71YatOQ5E/kNQeumCnI9XGHWeYWKr6QQ\u003d\u003d"}]